kyodonews.net 2015-12-20

# Privacy Policy | Kyodo News

We treat the information that users provide us with a high level of care, and use the information strictly within the terms of the privacy policy mentioned below.

We collect and record some data about our users' browsing activities and patterns. This is cumulative data, and does not identify any individual users. Users remain unidentifiable.

In order to improve our service, we will try to build a precise picture of the needs and preferences of our users by processing and analyzing data collected on the website. We will use data and its analysis for improving news coverage as well as tailoring this site better to users' preferences.

We share anonymous data with third parties whom we have contracted to provide us services, such as processing users' access-log data on the website.

When users respond by e-mail to sections or persons such as World Services Section or website editor, they leave their personal information including names, e-mail addresses. We use the information to communicate with users, but never share it with third parties.

As with many other websites, we use cookies, as they enable us to identify users when they visit the website. Cookies are small text files that are sent to users' browsers when the website is visited. Cookies are stored on users' hard disks. When users revisit the site, cookies will help them explore the site and support us to understand users' preferences and establish an audience picture of the website. If users do not wish to receive cookies from us, users can turn cookies off on their browser.

When users enter members' (subscribers') pages of the website, they will be requested to provide us their personal information like name, address, telephone number and so forth for registration on the website. This specific data will be recorded and accumulated in our system and will be shared only with Kyodo News, KK Kyodo News and Kyodo News International, but not with third parties at all.

The website contains links to other websites, and we are not responsible for the privacy practices on other sites. We recommend that you examine the privacy policies of the other websites you visit.

### About AP News Registry

This Web site uses services provided by AP News Registry. AP News Registry is based in the United States and collects content usage information and may use cookies and/or clear GIFs in conjuction with this activity. Your continued readership of this Site means you accept the privacy policy of the AP News Registry.
